# WIT   CODERS

## Opinionated Code Formatter

- Markdown 
- HTML 
  - HTML Main
  - HTML+CSS
  - HTML+Java Script
- CSS
 - C++

## Join Us ....

Time to get rewarded for contributing to the Open Source community!
 This repo seeks to document all of the companies giving away swag for Hacktoberfest 2020 and how you can get your hands on some free gifts for your time and help.


## Welcome ! This project is a beginner-friendly initiative: a fun , little  help you get creative with open source.

 ### HacktoberFest-2020
   
 - This is my first  Hacktoberfest.
   - What is Hacktoberfest?
   - Why should I contribute?
   - What can I contribute?
   - How to contribute in this repo.
  
  ## What is Hacktoberfest?
  Hacktoberfest is a month long virtual festival event to celebrate open source contributions. It is the easiest way to get into open source!
  
  During the entire month of October 2020, all you have to do is contribute to any open source projects and open at least 4 pull requests. Yes, any project and any kind of contributions.
  
## Why should I contribute?
The Hacktoberfest’s simple plain objective is: Support open source and earn a limited edition T-shirt! But, it’s not just about the t-shirts or stickers. Its about supporting open source. Its about celebrating open source, and giving it back. If you’ve never contributed to open source before, this is the perfect time to get started because Hacktoberfest provides a large list of available contribution opportunities.

## What can I contribute?
Hacktoberfest® is open to everyone in our global community. Whether you’re a developer, student learning to code. You can contribute to anything from code to simple fix, new feature to grammar mistake.

## How to contribute in this repo.
- Search for the repo you want .

-   Fork the repository.
    
- Clone your forked repository into your local machine.
    
- Take any issue from issues list or identify one.
    
-  Create a branch with a descriptive name (navbar-fix)
    
-  Write these commands on your terminal:
    
    git add -A (to stage your changes) git commit -m "very breif info of what youv'e done" git push origin master
    
- Then create your pull request.

-   Congratulations!! You have successfully created your pull request.  🌠


![](https://media.giphy.com/media/xUOxf7XfmpxuSode1O/giphy.gif)
## What if my pull requests aren’t accepted?

Even if your pull requests aren’t accepted, they should still count toward your 4 pull requests necessary to earn the shirt. The only exception would be if the project maintainer chooses to mark your pull request as “invalid”. They may do this if they perceive your pull request to be low effort, or if it contains plagiarism.

## What kinds of pull requests count toward earning the Hacktoberfest shirt?

Any pull request made to a public repo on GitHub will count. The pull request must contain commits you personally made yourself — not automated commits from bots.

You can contribute to any open source project hosted on Github.com and contribute anything between October 1 to October 31 midnight in 2020. You will find plenty of issues labeled with hacktoberfest or good-first-issue etc on Github. These will be the simple ones most probably and easy to fix.